That email you didn't send, the calculation you misread, the realisation that the deadline was yesterday... all followed by a sinking feeling, a quickening of the breath and the realisation that it's your fault.
那封你没有发出的邮件，你误读的计算结果，意识到截止日期是昨天……随之而来的是不祥的预感，呼吸加快，意识到这是你的错。
Fear not!
别怕！
Handled well, a mistake at work can become a great opportunity.
处理得当，工作中的错误可以变成一个绝佳的机会。
Start by owning up to it.
首先要勇于承认错误。
It may be tempting to cover up a mistake, but any deception is unlikely to last for long and could delay attempts to put right the problem.
掩盖错误可能很有诱惑性，但任何欺骗都不太可能持续很久，而且可能会延误尝试去解决问题。
And that's next – try to resolve the problems that you've created.
接下来就是——努力解决你自己造成的问题。
Being proactive and coming to your manager with suggestions is likely to help you regain trust.
积极主动地向你的经理提出建议，很可能有助于你重新获得信任。
Psychologists tell us that we tend to have a negativity bias – we are more likely to remember negative things.
心理学家告诉我们，我们往往有消极偏见——我们更容易记住消极的事情。
This is why executive coach Dina Denham Smith tells us we need to make our progress in fixing the issue clear and visible.
这就是为什么高管教练迪娜·德纳姆·史密斯告诉我们，我们需要让自己在解决问题上的进展清晰可见。
It's also important to apologise.
道歉也很重要。
Showing genuine remorse demonstrates that we can take ownership of our blunders.
表现出真诚的悔恨表明我们可以为自己的错误负责。
As well as looking at how we make amends for our mix-ups to other people, we also need to be honest with ourselves.
除了考虑如何弥补我们对他人的影响之外，我们也需要对自己诚实。
Removing emotion is important.
消除情绪很重要。
Shame from making a mistake can cloud our judgement when deciding how to respond.
因犯错而产生的羞耻感会在决定如何回应时影响我们的判断。
It can also affect our perception of the mistake's seriousness – it's easy to exaggerate how bad something really is.
它还会影响我们对错误严重性的认知——人们很容易夸大事情的糟糕程度。
Everyone makes mistakes.
每个人都会犯错。
What's really important is how we address them.
真正重要的是我们如何应对错误。
It's important to be reflective.
进行反思很重要。
Consider if there's an underlying cause for the mistake, and how to prevent future slip-ups.
考虑错误是否有潜在的原因，以及如何防止将来出现失误。
It can also be useful to seek advice from someone who's had similar experiences in the past.
向有过类似经历的人寻求建议也可能很有用。
Combined with our own reflections, this can be a powerful way to grow in our job and be more successful.
加上我们自己的反思，这可以成为在工作中成长并取得更大成功的有效途径。
Academics Jasmine Virhia and Grace Lordan highlight research showing that workplaces which replace fear and blame around mistakes with opportunities for self-reflection are more psychologically safe.
学者贾斯敏·维尔希亚和格蕾丝·洛丹提请人们注意一项研究，该研究表明用自我反思的机会取代对错误的恐惧和责备的工作场所，会令人在心理上感到更加安全。
This allows people to learn from their mistakes, grow their skills, improve processes and ultimately productivity.
这使人们能够从错误中学习，提升技能，改进流程，最终提高生产力。
Handled in the right way, by both employees and employers, mistakes can become a powerful tool for improvement.
如果员工和雇主都处理得当，错误可以成为进步的有效工具。